

# El Mehdi Douiri

## **Developer Full Stack JAVA**

20-year-old developer with a BTS in Information Systems Development. Pursuing higher education in EST while enrolled in JobinTech for full-stack Java development. Passionate about software development, showcased through diverse projects in my portfolio. Eager to explore new opportunities and collaborations.

#### **Contact Info**

- 0636784324 0614215996
- elmehdidouiri99@gmail.com elmehdi.douiri@jobintech-uir.ma
- rhttps://drelmido001.github.io/elmehdidouiri/

## **Education**

### **Higher University Degree**

2024 - Present

#### Senior Technician Certificate

2023

## **High School Diploma**

2021

#### **Skills**

#### Front End Development

HTML-CSS-Javascript-XML-Angular

## **Back End Development**

JAVA-PHP-VB.net

#### Conception

UML-Merise-Gestion de projet

#### **SGBD**

MYSQL-SQLSEVER

## **Experiences**

JOBINTECH UIR - Full stack JAVA/ANGULAR
March 2024 - Present

Mastered Full Stack development in 4-month Java-SpringBoot/Angular program. Proficient in Java, SpringBoot for backend, and Angular for frontend. Skilled in designing, developing, and deploying dynamic web applications.

Internship at A.R.E.F june 2023

Developed a desktop application for managing incoming/outgoing mail within the office of order (using VB.NET) during an internship at the Regional Academy of Education and Training of Tangier Tetouan Al Hoceima.

Final Project2022 - 2023

I developed a Java-based mobile app for dairy product distribution management, streamlining inventory, orders, and delivery logistics with MySQL backend and XML frontend for efficient operations.

#### **For More Information**



This Barcode Redirecto to My Personal Website